[Music]
man this is going to be so [__] epic
yeah we should totally go swimming
obviously we're going swimming you
[__] [__] what else did you think we
were going to do at a water park
obviously you [__] douchebag I was
just being
rhetorical well then don't well I'm sure
there's boatloads other things for us to
do besides swimming I mean dude don't
give me that just last week you were so
pumped about riding the waves oh I think
I know what's up our fearless leader is
afraid of getting his feet wet because
he's a fatty and he'll sink like a
bowling
ball don't think for any mine big blue
hey how about we hit the concession
stand first I hear the G chocolate tacos
I know how much you love those things
which is really funny since you are not
Mexican
y they may not know how to run a country
but they sure know how to make good food
oh God I can't contain my
excitement oh baby brother it's funny
how even though I am older you're always
the one looking out for
me excuse me sir I would like to order
one dozen of your lovely ice cream tacos
so that my cute little bro here can
stuff his chubby cheek
what the [__] are you doing yo Knuckles
what are you doing here what's it look
like I'm working cuse I don't get a mom
to L off of like you retards manic why
are you groping your bro fat ass I'm not
doing anything of the sort Sonic do you
know he's touching your huge butt what
no he isn't I would feel it he just
pulled his hand away don't listen to him
bro he's just trying to cause a wedge
between us because he's jealous he
doesn't have a bro as cool as you that
is [__] oh my god look everyone it's
part
lebby good gracious will everyone please
move out of the way I'm just going to
purchase an ice
cream hello I would like to purchase one
of your finest red white and blue bum
Pops in honor of the Fallen American
Heroes you have change for a $50,000
bill BMB pop is $2 oh I hate when this
happens I guess I'll just purchase the
whole water park to balance it out one
bumb up on the stick please I got you
[Music]
boss here you go one fresh BM pop
perfect for cooling down on a hot day
I must say that was quite frankly yummy
for a cheap frozen dessert that costs
only $50,000 what a value you're
practically giving these things away to
rich people go my beach I didn't even
see you there look at you rocking that
really small tight Speedo you look
fantastic hey do you want to come watch
me swim in the shallow end of the pool
watch you swim he that sounds like a lot
of fun I know did you notice that I said
the shallow end because you can't swim I
did you're always looking out for me
dear it's one of my favorite things
about you cool beans now put this bum
pop up in your ass I want to save it for
later make sure you wedge it up deep in
there now so it doesn't fall on the
floor and get
dirty hey Beach have you ever whipped
out your balls and pissed in a public
pool before haha of course not Bart leby
that seems so
unsanitary that's exactly what makes the
prank so funny the idea of a stranger
swimming through your PE is very comical
dare me to do it n that's fine okay I'm
going to do it anyway here I
[Applause]
go aha Bart lebby what's with that face
don't tell me you actually peed in the
public pool D PE yeah pee in the pool
that's all I did
you're so silly hopefully no one swims
through the warm spot hey maybe we
should get out but why would we do that
love I only just dipped my toes season I
I think someone [__] their pants in the
pool someone pooped wait Bart will be
did did you just crap in the [__]
pool what of of course not baby what
would ever give you that idea well the
water turned brown after you gotten
water is just like there sometimes Bach
you just wouldn't know that because you
don't go swimming that much water can
come in many shades of color just like
people okay but you literally just said
you think someone pooped so I'm going to
go talk to the Lifeguard and get that
terrible terrible man thrown out of
here get over here you damn homosexual
[Music]
[__] my [__] Bach are you all right
art leby what happened to me the
terrible man who pooped in the water
heard you were going to snitch on him he
dragged you down under the water in an
attempt to drown you luckily I was there
to chase the mean man away I think you
owe your sex oh Bartleby what I don't
want to swim anymore pools are scary I
think I think I want to go home oh [__]
pools aren't scary actually they can be
fun and relaxing too they can [__]
allow me to show you the mystical
wonders of the Lazy
River oh my Bartleby just what are these
magnificent Donuts h no [__] they may
look deceivingly scrumptious but they
are not Donuts these are what you poor
people call River tubes they are shaped
like but holes so that you can sit in
them with your ass you mean I don't have
to swim at a water park to have fun nope
things are different here in the Lazy
River then I want to sit in this yellow
one it's gold in color just like your
hair will symbolize my the stability I
feel whenever you are around it's funny
in a way it's more than just a floating
device it's a symbol a symbol of my love
for you
Bartleby okay I'm getting this poop
green one cause it looks like
money oh what a boy boy you know it's
unfortunate that everyone can't just
have big fatties like
us yeah boobies are like helium fil
balloons no matter how hard we try to
sink they keep us buoyant yeah we don't
even need to try to float AB boobs do
all the work for us like can you imagine
the lifeguards trying to rescue us you'd
be all like no no sir my boobs have got
this he M have you noticed something
about Flora lately I think she's feeling
a bit overshadowed by our glorious
assets [__] [__] not everyone can be
well endowed as us
I am not jealous everyone knows a girl's
worth isn't defined by her appearance
physical attributes may be a part of who
we are but they don't determine our
value as individuals they's so much more
to us than just how we look you're only
saying that cause you don't have what
mini and I have yeah small boobs and a
big mouth that's all you've got maybe I
am jealous but not because of your tests
I'm jealous of the bond you to share but
the way you always use it to gang up the
me I just wish I had that now if you
need me which I doubt you will cause me
never do I'll be putting on my sunscreen
in the bathroom where no one can judge
me based on the measurements of my
properly developed chest yeah give me a
heck get on in there [__] then tell me
how bad it stinks
hey now that wasn't very nice just let
it go say yeah it's just how girls are
they live their lives by the son of Envy
that's why they end up being [__] men
are better because we live by the bro
code which dictates all disputes must be
settled in the most manly ways possible
shirtless and in the parking lot of a
dick sport T Goods where you beat each
other's ass and then go down to the
diner for some onion rings and a Cherry
Cola God men are so cool yeah we have
ball sacks while girls have to pee out
of their
butts Flora it's me Sonia I saw what
happened with you and your sisters can
we talk yeah I'm just using the bathroom
give me a few
minutes Flora as a fellow female I'm
really sorry you had to go through
something like that but you know it's
okay cuz everyone already knows you have
small breasts I appreciate the kind
gesture but can you please close the
door well damn if you're going to be a
[__] about it then maybe you don't
deserve my guidance you know our breasts
may appear to be the same size but I'm
about 30% smaller in general since I'm a
hedgehog and you're some all blue
crypted thing so mathematically speaking
my breasts are way bigger than yours
when compared to my own body's
proportions think on that while you take
your piss you're [__]
[__] you see [__] nothing bad ever
happens here on the Lazy River oh you
are so right dear but man that sun is
beaming I'm starting to think I should
have put on some
sunscreen oh my my little muffin cake if
you wanted me to rub lotion all over
your niky body all you had to do was
[Music]
ask hey my buom
pop how strange I don't remember
ordering this buom pop Di dipped in
chocolate
fudge oh that's not half bad I might
have to order it like this more often
[__] oh no his lower half is so [__]
fat that he is unable to flip himself
back over hang on [__] dad is coming
please remain seated in your inner tub
at all times but my boyfriend is
drowning aren't you going to do
something well do you have proof that
he's drowning he's upside down in the
water well I don't hear him screaming
that's because he's upside down in the
water okay well what do you want me to
do about it I want you to save his life
no why not because I saw you guys sneak
food into the lazy river and that is
against the rules I was going to throw
you out but then I noticed you were
lovers and I thought it was absurdly
cute that you guys were on the Lazy
River together but I'm done being nice
cause that gets you nowhere in life well
time for my break but I'll be watching
so you better not leave that in her tube
or else I'm telling every lifeguard in
the park please help us manic Knuckles
anyone help us hey Sonia the Hedgehog my
sister Mindy put in a good word for you
how would you like to make some cold
Hard Cash sorry Mandy I don't do casual
sex with strangers hauh not that Sonia
we just want you to help us kill Flora
kill Flora what the actual [__] are you
saying
Sonia not so loud haha killing someone
has to be done in secret you know but
why her what did she do because if the
bit dies everything she owns will be
passed over to us does she even have
anything to give you lay it on her sis
Flora has $87 worth of ins old girl
scout cookies and we're willing to let
you in on the job but Flora is my friend
that's exactly why I recommended you
Sonia you part of her in a CA no one
will suspect a thing if you vote for us
help us put an end to this [__] and
we'll give you 3% of the
$87 you're offering me
$261 to help you commit murder it's a
limited time offer take it or leave it
you two are unbelievable I refuse to
Snuff out an innocent life for pocket
change it's not Pocket Change you can
buy like two things with that kind of
money if you're in a Dollar Tree [__]
have you been in a Dollar Tree things
cost 125 now and with tax I won't even
be able to buy two things we'll give her
a V8 with poison that [__] loves Vates
I'm going to go down the water slide now
if I don't come out of the other side
it's probably because my massive Titar
stuck somewhere halfway through so have
911 on speed
dial here Sonia let's look over the edge
and see her come out from the the other
side yeah okay that sounds like
fun maybe she's still going down it is a
pretty tall water
slide oh my God don't worry she'll be
okay if she lands on her boobs
Mand Lor is dead I'm really sorry about
you your sister well a part of me always
feared something like this would happen
Mandy you know her breasts were so big
it was only a matter of time before
something went wrong I'm just surprised
it didn't happen sooner I always said
normal size breasts aren't so bad after
all you know what screw your rules I
don't care if I get get in trouble I
don't even care if you throw me out
because my [__] needs me then why don't
you prove it leave that inner tube and
shows me how strong Your Love really is
okay I will watch
this oh [__] he's actually doing
it you did it Bartleby you saved my life
I did B I did but I fear it came at a
great cost how so they said if I saved
your life I would have to go home and I
didn't care you know why why because I
why don't interrupt me and I'll tell you
because I love you
okay what is this b b you passed the
test I always heard you put your [__]
above all else and I always wanted to
see for myself whether that was true or
not now that I see you here in the lesi
river with your [__] those Legends
weren't Legend at all they were very
real please enjoy the rest of the day
and swim to your hearts content you
amazing homosexual man thank you no
baral B I should be the one thanking you
because I've never seen a love so pure
in my life you have single-handedly
given me hope that love can still exist
in this crazy world of ours you're
welcome now what do you say we get a
move on beach I hear the fireworks sure
is about to begin
hey Knuckles are you almost done setting
up the bottle rockets yet all set for
the firework sh boss tell the hype man
to get on out there and get those
[__] pumped cool cool although
there's one knocked down over there make
sure you pick that one up before we set
them all off so we don't have any form
of accident Orit it'll be fine if I
stick around here I won't be able to see
the fireworks for myself
hey knuckles I guess this mean you're
done with work hell yeah this is going
to be one explosive night if you catch
my
drift here party people it's me crazy
[__] a who's ready for the best fire mer
of this
summer couple guys this is super party
we've all been waiting for let's hear
such voice for the summer
pleas I get it no but to it and that's
okay I'm crazy you got I know let's
inside of the
can't let me
here okay not bad not bad how my drive
side can you be
[Music]
F now that's more like
the ready for St fight
let's Dr it out
together
7 oh God there's a firework down over
there I have to warn everyone before we
all
perish yeah that's more like this come
on party L stone now the Big 3
2 1
B leby what's happening a firework was
down Bach a firework was down we must
live from this fiery Skillet or else we
will be roasted with the rest of the
fools before today we Associated water
parks with lter and the cool relief from
summer heat we ran through the Bloodshed
I kept my eyes closed so I willn't see
the body parts
[Applause]
flying a place where water flows in
abundance designed to soak and Drench
engulfed by fiery
Flames be not afraid for I Creator
himself gave us special gifts to C these
evil Flames everyone whip out your ball
we're going to peek on the fire and
clear
[Applause]
PA look down there the boys are using
their penises to put out the fire
[Applause]
[Music]
I guess it's true what they say Boys
Rule and girls
[Music]
drule I've been loving everything you
are
are your eyes are of the brightest
stars I could set you all
night just drinking in your
[Music]
sunlight can we love tonight you put all
the stars in my eyes can we love tonight
you tell me I light up the whole sky can
we love tonight you put all the stars in
my eyes can we love tonight you tell me
a light of the sky
[Music]